IHEME DORIS EZIAKU

CONTENT CREATOR, SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER & GRAPHICS DESIGNER.

Lekki, Lagos | mailto: dorisiheme14@gmail.com | +2348157474347, +2349039152334

My Portfolio

EDUCATION

Federal University of Technology Owerri | Bachelor of Engineering

Owerri, Imo State | 2018 - Present

SKILLS

Tools & Platforms:

Social Media Management: Proficient in managing and optimizing social media platforms to drive brand growth.

Graphics design: Proficient in creating visually appealing designs for digital and company growth.

Content creation: Creative storyteller adept at making well written and visual content across platforms.

Cinematography/photography: Skilled in capturing stunning visuals through photography and cinematography.

Event planning: proficient in organizing all events including meetings. skilled in time/budget management.

E-marketing: Skilled in executing organised e-marketing campaigns and utilizing data-driven insights.

Project management: Experienced in delivering cross-functional projects on time and within budget.

EXPERIENCE

ACE-FUELS | Social Media Manager

Nigeria | Jun 2022 - Present

- Create, develop, implement and publish contents on all platforms
- submission of content at stipulated day and time.
- analysing page performance and reporting feedback.
- manage the day-to-day handling of all social media channels.
- submission of monthly performance for review.
- follow up on recent trends, awards and discoveries on foreign and national pages.
- engaging in research developments on new ways to sustain the platform.
- form key relationship with promoters.
- identifying customer trend to help with planning social media campaigns.
- initiating reminders for post.

FUTO | Personal Assistant

Nigeria Jun 2019 - May 2022

- scheduling appointments.
- maintaining office systems.
- helping with time and daily managements.
- attending to scheduled appointments when unavailable.
- assisting with office work.

INTERESTS

Music: I enjoy listening to music even while working, I love Rock and Pop Music.

SUMMARY

Highly skilled and versatile professional with a diverse range of talents in social media management, e-marketing, content creation, project management, graphic design, photography, and cinematography. I possess a keen eye for aesthetics and a passion for storytelling. With a strong track record of driving digital engagement and producing visually stunning content, I bring a unique blend of creativity, technical expertise, and project management skills to elevate brands and captivate audiences. Let's connect and discuss how I can contribute to your organization's success.